Now, you've defined a neural network in model.py,
在 model.py 中定义了神经网络后
it's time to instantiate and train that model,
下面实例化并训练该模型
and we'll do this in the training script which is a file that's
我们将在训练脚本中完成操作
located in the source directory under train.py.
该文件位于 source 目录的 train.py 下
The training script is key for training a custom model.
训练脚本是训练自定义模型的关键
It's the script that will execute when.fit is called on a custom estimator.
当我们对自定义 estimator 调用 .fit 时 该脚本将执行
Now, I'll be showing you a PyTorch example but you can also train and
下面我将演示一个 PyTorch 示例 但是你也可以
deploy custom scikit-learn models in a very similar way.
以非常相似的方式训练和部署自定义 scikit-learn 模型
In fact, it's even easier because you can just import a model instead of defining
实际上更简单 因为只需导入模型 而不用定义自定义模型
a custom one and mini Sklearn models have built in predict functions.
很多 Sklearn 模型都有内置的预测函数
So the only file you'll need is a train.py file.
唯一需要完成的是 train.py 文件
So a typical training script is responsible for a number of things.
典型的训练脚本会完成多项操作
First, it loads in your training data and it will parse any training
首先 它会加载训练数据
and model hyperparameters that are passed into your estimator constructor,
并解析传入 estimator 构造函数的所有训练和模型超参数
then it will instantiate a model with any specified hyperparameters,
然后它将根据指定的超参数实例化模型
in our case things like input dim,
我们的参数包括 input_dim
hidden dim and output dim and it will train that model.
Hidden_dim 和 output_dim 然后训练该模型
Finally, it's also responsible for
最后 它还负责
saving the trained model so that it can be deployed later.
保存训练过的模型 以便稍后部署模型
So let's take a look at this train.py file.
我们看看 train.py 文件
The first thing in here are my inputs.
首先是 import 语句
Any libraries I need and aligned to input the model that we just made, SimpleNet.
导入我需要的库并导入刚刚创建的模型 SimpleNet
Then I have a couple of provided functions
然后是提供的几个函数
including a function that loads a previously trained model.
这个函数会加载之前训练过的模型
This is helpful if you want to create a SimpleNet from previously saved model parameters.
如果你想根据之前保存的模型参数创建 SimpleNet 那么这个函数很有用
The next thing I have is get train loader which accepts
然后是函数 _get_train_loader
a batch size and a data directory where our training data is saved.
它的参数包括批次大小和训练数据的保存位置
This function will read in a training CSV file which it assumes is
这个函数将读取训练 csv 文件
called train.csv and it will split it into labels and features.
它认为叫做 train.csv 并将其划分为标签和特征
Here I'm getting labels from the first column of data and our features from the rest.
在这里从第一列获取标签并从剩余列中获取特征
Then I'm wrapping my features and labels into
然后将特征和标签放入 TensorDataset 中
a TensorDataset which can be easily batched by a data loader.
便于 DataLoader 批处理这些特征和标签
Next, I have a train function which takes in a model,
接下来是 train 函数
our trained loader, and some training parameters.
它的参数包括模型 train_loader 以及训练参数
This loop is responsible for iterating over all of
这个循环负责遍历所有的训练数据
our training data and updating the model according to some optimization parameters.
并根据优化参数更新模型
So here for example,
例如在这里
I'm looking at how my model response to a batch of data and
查看模型对一批数据的响应效果
I'm looking at how close the output is to some target,
并查看输出与某个目标的接近程度
then in performing back propagation and optimization to improve the model.
然后执行反向传播和优化步骤 改进模型
I also have a line here to print out some stats about training,
这行代码将输出训练信息
and I'm actually going to collapses for a better visibility.
收起这部分 这样看起来更整洁
But only at the end of all of our epics,
但仅在所有训练周期之后
I'm going to save our trained model to a model directory,
将训练过的模型保存到模型目录下
and they have some provided saving functions here.
这里提供了一些保存函数
Saving the State Dictionary of a trained model and just saving the model parameters.
保存训练过的模型的状态字典以及仅保存模型参数
Now, all the details about how to actually define a model entry in it,
这个主 if 语句中包含了所有的详细信息
how many epics to train for and so on,
包括如何定义和训练模型
all of those taken care of in this main if statement,
要训练多少个周期 等等
if name equals main.
if _name_ == ‘_main_’
All of the code in here is what will execute when you
当你调用 .fit 来训练自定义 estimator 时
call.fit and train a custom estimator.
所有这些代码将执行
So in this if statement,
我将在此 if 语句中
is where I wanted to find all my model and training hyperparameters.
定义所有的模型和训练超参数
These will be arguments like batch size that will be able to
这些参数包括 batch-size
parse into a constructor when we create an estimator.
当我们创建 estimator 时 这些参数将传入构造函数中
This will also be where I get my train loader and
我将在这里获取 train_loader
instantiate a model with some specify parameters.
并用指定的参数实例化模型
I'll have to define an optimizer and loss function and parse
我需要定义优化器和损失函数
those to my train function above to finally save my trained model.
并将它们传递给上面的 train 函数 最终保存训练过的模型
So you have a few to dos in here,
你需要完成几个 TODO 任务
and your first task will be to define the model and training
第一个任务是在这里定义模型和训练超参数
hyperparameters and add them to our unknown argument here.
并将它们添加到 args 里
You can do this with an ArgumentParser.
你可以使用 ArgumentParser
This ArgumentParser basically allows us to add arguments to our estimator constructor.
借助 ArgumentParser 你可以将参数添加到 estimator 构造函数中
So we can add things like batch size,
我们可以添加 batch-size 等
but we can specify when we actually construct a custom estimator.
当我们实际构造自定义 estimator 时可以指定这些参数
To add an argument,
为了添加参数
we just need to call parser.add argument and parse
我们只需调用 parser.add_argument
in dash dash and the name of a variable and a few other things.
并传入双短线和变量的名称以及其他几项内容
Each argument has a type something like int or string,
每个参数都有一个类型 例如 int 或 string
a default value that it can take if it's not specified in the constructor.
一个默认值 在构造函数中没有指定值时就采用默认值
A metavar, which is a descriptive string typically a letter or two like n
一个 metavar 它是一个描述性字符串 通常是一两个字母
for number or s for seed that may be used in usage messages.
例如 n 表示数字 s 表示 seed 它们可以用在用法消息中
Finally, help, which is just a description about what this parameter is.
最后是 help 它是描述参数的一句话
In this first batch of arguments,
第一批参数
we have actually SageMaker Parameters.
都是 SageMaker 参数
These are things like the model directory in the data directory,
例如模型目录和数据目录
where we can find training data and place our trained model output.
分别表示训练数据的存储位置以及训练模型输出的存储位置
These are things that will be set automatically no matter the estimator.
无论是什么 estimator 这些参数都会自动设置
Then I've set some training arguments things like batch size,
然后是一些训练参数 例如 batch-size
the number of epics to train for, and a learning rate.
训练周期数和学习速率
Your task will be to add new parameters that we need to define a SimpleNet,
你的任务是添加定义 SimpleNet 所需的新参数
essentially like we had to parse in k for a k-means
例如传入 k，表示 k 均值模型
model or a predictor type for training a linear learner.
以及训练 LinearLearner 的预测器类型
We know that we have three model parameters that define the input,
我们有三个模型参数
hidden and output dimensions,
分别定义了输入 隐藏和输出维度
so you should add three new arguments here.
你应该在这里添加三个新的参数
I recommend naming them according to the parameters in our SimpleNet,
建议根据 SimpleNet 中的参数名称命名
so input dim hidden dim and output dim.
所以分别为 input_dim hidden_dim 和 output_dim
Your next to do is to actually instantiate
下个 TODO 任务是实例化该模型
the model by passing in those input parameters,
并传入这些输入参数
so you can call simple myth and passing something like
可以调用 SimpleNet 并传入参数
args.inputdim to get the appropriate dimension.
例如 args.input_dim 以获得相应的维度
Finally, you'll define an optimizer and criterion for training.
最后定义训练优化器和损失函数
All of these things will be packed into your train function here,
所有这些都放入 train 函数里
which takes care of training and saving your model.
它将负责训练和保存模型
Next, try to complete this training script following the to dos marked in code.
接下来请根据代码中的 TODO 标记完成此训练脚本
Then, I'll show you one possible solution next.
然后我将介绍我的一种解决方案